sup everyone Timothy 3 4 5 here with a
very special video today
now I've been wanting to make this video
and I've been wanting to make this video
for a very long time addressing what
people are saying about my accent or my
voice or whatever the hell you want to
call that and and it's God you
won't do it people are like bullying me
and like I don't give a what
you think people people are like
Tambor's what is your accent like are
you are you what are you black like like
are you are you Australian or some
shut the up like my
momma told me people tell me all the
time that I sound like obi-wan Kenobi
from Star Wars just last week my momma
was like you sound like qui-gon
jinn like like I don't know why people
think people got to the point - it's bad
people say your voice is stupid people
think it's like but people think I'm
trying too hard the sound guy I mean
like you you living together for
five minutes and see how your voice
turns out like maybe I did grow up in
the God oh maybe I'm like
maybe you're like
you you don't control me you're a little
like you're like if you think my accent
is stupid I think you're a little
you can kiss my ass
I mean like like like I sometimes I
even get like 10 20 maybe even 30
comments are day of people saying like
your voice is stupid
well you know what I say to that I say
all 45 of you your voices are
stupid you guys are in the comments
section
and and they have you heard your
voices no no you haven't heard
each other's voices so just because I'm
more famous than you
you think it's you have the right to say
that you know that my voice is stupid
my mama says I sound like kwan-jin
do you sound like waa no you don't do
you sound like oh whoa no you
sound like the Yoda you pick it up what
I'm putting down you picking it
up pick it up bend over and pick it up
oh I will kick your ass what I'm
saying is this don't do not make
people put people down just because you
think that voice is better than yours
okay do are we clear here I think we are
cuz if not I think we're gonna have a
problem do you understand
another thing people like to say to us
why do you say and at the end of
every phrasing like that example
like I say last week I was walking out
straight and I saw and I met Almonte
offense so you know what I did I beat
his ass and people say why do you
add though phrase and at the end
and you know why because I'm never done
I've never done be just like when if I
say add
you do not know what I'm gonna say next
you know why because I I am like the
only soccer friend laughing and I
am doing whatever I can to bring back
sock on the ground so so people they
look at me and think wow famous that
that guy is amazing and he's like
you just don't know what he's gonna do
next he's crazy like like that's right
unlike you are you
let's say that I'm the crazy one no
like I am normal if anything
you're the normal ones and me being
weird makes me different and different
is good
do you understand how you poopy baby
do you need me to change the
topic you poopy baby is that how
hard for you can understand is that is
that why cuz you little poopy baby
who afraid of you don't
understand we live in a society where
people are afraid of what they don't
understand and because of that even if
somebody has a different voice than them
and they're like I don't like that
person
well you know what I don't like
you nobody likes you
everybody hates you and you know
why I hate you because because you're
normal and normal is bad sorry
about cutting off like that I had to
poop a little bit anyways a back I was
saying more than oh yeah one thing about
this world that makes it good is that
some people have different voices and
for example let's say you go into a
Taco Bell lock like it your baby
stepping through Mexico in that point
and odds are like you bashed me about my
voice let yet if you step into a Taco
Bell odds are you will learn at least
not two or three Max in words like like
in an instant like like like your like
your money the word taco you'll you're
gonna burrito like the cup size is our
small medium and grande do you know what
Grande is like I'm that's Mexican
that's Mexican like big or some
like oh I don't know I don't give a
anyways yeah that's all I wanted